

💌 FrostBDonovan@gmail.com | 🧥 fdonovan98.github.io/portfolio | 🖸 FDonovan98 | 🛆 frostdonovan | 🛅 frost-donovan

## Summary.

I am a passionate Producer with a background in programming, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. I have been using my time post graduation to recover from burnout, as well as expanding my knowledge of Art Production. My ideal position would be an Associate Producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience to progress to a more senior position.

#### Skills

- · Agile Management: User Stories, Story Points, Velocity, Sprint & Release Planning & Review, Scrum, CD Pipelines
- Software: Jira, Confluence, Git, Trello, GitHub & Bitbucket, Google & Microsoft Suite
- · Art Software: Blender, Substance Painter, Clip Studio Paint
- Languages: C#, C++, Latex, Github Actions
- Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4

### Published Games \_\_\_

Castan - Producer

Unity 2020.3

Published June 2021

September 2021 - May 2022

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1836170/CASTAN/)

- · Utilised Story Points & Velocity, Release Planning, and Jira to manage scope
- Facilitated & assisted with several significant redesigns
- · Developed a Github Action workflow to automatically build, test & publish daily builds to Steam

Carma - Producer Unity 2019.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)

· Shortlisted for the Grads In Games Student Game Award

- · Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game
- Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile
- Removed blockers and streamlined development pipelines
- Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- Set up Steam store and maintained updated builds

#### Awards

Finalist, Grads In Games Student Game Award

#### Education

#### **Falmouth University** BSC COMPUTING FOR GAMES

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

· Worked with multi-discipline teams to bring several games through a full development cycle

- · Published two to Steam, one of which was shortlisted for Grads In Games Student Game Award
- · Wrote a dissertation on Continuous Delivery (CD) In Student Teams, implementing and analysing the effect of CD pipelines
- Graduated with a 2:1 Honours

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

GLASS NOMAD GAMES

Falmouth, Cornwall March 2021 - Current

- Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing
- · Managed company accounts and government-required paperwork
- Handled Steam registration, set up, and backend work for multiple titles

#### Senior Ambassador

Falmouth, Cornwall

June 2020 - September 2021

FXPLUS

Director

- Responsible for the smooth running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- · Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

FROST DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ JULY 21, 2022